A Guide to the Spelman Fund of New York records FA063
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects, 1925-1970; 4
  - Projects - General Projects, 4.1
    - Fellowships - Reeder, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Fellowships - Stutz, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - Fellowships - Toll, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - Fellowships - Vinck, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Fellowships - Von Leyden, 1933-1935 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Fellowships - White, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Fellowships - Woodbury, 1935-1937 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Governor of the State of Maine, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Governor of the State of Maine, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 266)
    - Governor of the State of Maine, 1931-1935 (Box 8, Folder 267)
    - Governor's Commission on County Government - Ohio, 1933-1935 (Box 8, Folder 268)
    - Great Island Conference, 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 269)
    - Illinois Housing Commission, 1932-1933 (Box 8, Folder 270)
    - Industrial Commission of Minnesota, 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 271)
    - Industrial Commission of Minnesota, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 272)
    - Industrial Commission of Minnesota, 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Industrial Commission of Minnesota - Reports (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Industrial Commission of the State of New York, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    - Industrial Commission of the State of New York, 1932-1933 (Box 9, Folder 276)
    - Industrial Commission of the State of New York, 1934-1935 (Box 9, Folder 277)
    - Industrial Commission of the State of New York - Reports (Box 9, Folder 278)
    - Industrial Commission of the State of New York - Reports (Box 9, Folder 279)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1932-1934 (Box 9, Folder 280)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 281)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 282)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 283)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 284)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London, 1940-1949 (Box 9, Folder 285)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Scope for Initiative in the Junior Grades of the Civil Service" by Thomas E. Naughten, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 285A)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "A Day in My Official Life" by Officers of the Public Service, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 285B)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Decentralisation in Government Departments" by May L. Dhonau, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 285C)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Staff Reports in the Public Service", 1936 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Essays on Aspects of Public Administration", 1935 (Box 10, Folder 285E)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Expected Population Changes and Their Effect Upon Social Services" by Norman Wilson, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 285)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Stabilisation of Rates" by E. J. D. Lloyd, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 285G)
    - Institute of Public Administration, London - Report - "Use of Sinking Funds, &c., for Capital Purposes" by Ernest Long and Eric Maxwell, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 285H)
    - Institute of Public Administration, New York - Scandinavian Study, 1934-1942 (Box 10, Folder 286)
    - Joint Committee for the Cooperation of the League of California Municipalities, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 287)
    - Joint Committee for the Cooperation of the League of California Municipalities - Reports (Box 10, Folder 288)
    - Joint Committee on Municipal Reporting, 1929-1931 (Box 10, Folder 289)
    - Joint Committee on Planning and Cooperation of the International Union of Local Authorities and the International Institute of Administrative Science, 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 290)
    - Joint Committee on Planning and Cooperation, 1936-1970 (Box 11, Folder 291)
    - Joint Committee on Planning and Cooperation - Reports (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council, 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council, 1935 (Box 11, Folder 294)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council, 1938-1941 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council - Reports (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council - Reports (Box 12, Folder 299)
    - Kansas State Planning Board and Kansas Legislative Council - Reports (Box 12, Folder 300)
    - Kentucky Legislative Council, 1936-1940 (Box 12, Folder 301)
    - Kentucky Legislative Council - Reports (Box 12, Folder 302)
    - League of California Municipalities, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 303)
    - League of California Municipalities, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 304)
    - League of California Municipalities, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 305)
    - League of California Municipalities, 1937-1940 (Box 12, Folder 306)
    - League of California Municipalities - Reports (Box 12, Folder 307)
    - League of California Municipalities - Audits, 1934-1939 (Box 13, Folder 308)
    - League of Minnesota Municipalities, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 309)
    - League of Minnesota Municipalities, 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 310)
    - League of Minnesota Municipalities, 1933-1934 (Box 13, Folder 311)
    - League of Minnesota Municipalities, 1935-1938 (Box 13, Folder 312)
    - League of Minnesota Municipalities - Reports (Box 13, Folder 313)
    - League of Oregon Cities, 1930-1934 (Box 13, Folder 314)
    - League of Oregon Cities, 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 315)
    - League of Oregon Cities, 1937-1940 (Box 13, Folder 316)
    - League of Oregon Cities - Reports (Box 13, Folder 317)
    - League of Texas Municipalities, 1929-1934 (Box 14, Folder 318)
    - League of Texas Municipalities, 1935-1940 (Box 14, Folder 319)
    - League of Texas Municipalities - Bulletins and Reports (Box 14, Folder 320)
    - League of Texas Municipalities - Audits, 1935-1939 (Box 14, Folder 321)
    - League of Virginia Counties, 1936-1937 (Box 14, Folder 322)
    - League of Virginia Counties, 1938-1940 (Box 14, Folder 323)
    - League of Virginia Counties - Reports (Box 14, Folder 324)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 325)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities, 1931-1934 (Box 14, Folder 326)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities, 1935-1937 (Box 14, Folder 327)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Annual Reports, 1932-1940 (Box 15, Folder 329)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Annual Reports, 1932-1940 (Box 15, Folder 330)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Annual Reports, 1932-1940 (Box 15, Folder 331)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Audits, 1931-1940 (Box 15, Folder 332)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Audits, 1931-1940 (Box 15, Folder 333)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Reports (Box 15, Folder 334)
    - League of Virginia Municipalities - Institute of Public Affairs, 1931-1933 (Box 15, Folder 335)
    - Mayor's Committee on City Planning - New York, 1934-1935 (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - Michigan Municipal League, 1930-1941 (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - Michigan Municipal League, 1930-1941 (Box 16, Folder 338)
    - Michigan Municipal League, 1930-1941 (Box 16, Folder 339)
    - Michigan Municipal League, 1930-1941 (Box 16, Folder 340)
    - Michigan Municipal League, 1930-1941 (Box 16, Folder 341)
    - Michigan Municipal League - Audits, 1932-1941 (Box 16, Folder 342)
    - Michigan Municipal League - Audits, 1932-1941 (Box 16, Folder 343)
    - Michigan Municipal League - Reports (Box 16, Folder 344)
    - Michigan Municipal League - Reports (Box 16, Folder 345)
    - Michigan State Commission of Inquiry, 1931-1936 (Box 17, Folder 346)
    - Michigan State Commission of Inquiry, 1931-1936 (Box 17, Folder 347)
    - Michigan State Commission of Inquiry, 1931-1936 (Box 17, Folder 348)
    - Michigan State Commission of Inquiry - Reports (Box 17, Folder 349)
    - Michigan State Commission of Inquiry - Reports (Box 17, Folder 350)
    - Minnesota Division of Administrative Management, 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 351)
    - Minnesota Division of Administrative Management, 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 352)
    - Minnesota Division of Administrative Management - Pamphlets and Reports (Box 17, Folder 353)
    - National Institute of Public Administration - Williamsburg Survey, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 354)
    - National Municipal League - Municipal Administration Service, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - National Municipal League - Municipal Administration Service, 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 356)
    - National Municipal League - Municipal Administration Service - Reports and Pamphlets (Box 18, Folder 357)
    - New York Commission on Old Age Security, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 358)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers, 1929-1937 (Box 18, Folder 359)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers, 1929-1937 (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers, 1929-1937 (Box 18, Folder 361)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers - Annual Report, 1931-1935 (Box 18, Folder 362)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers - Audits, 1931-1935 (Box 18, Folder 363)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers - Reports (Box 18, Folder 364)
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officers - Reports (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - New York State Planning Board, 1934-1935 (Box 19, Folder 366)
    - New York State Planning Board - Reports (Box 19, Folder 367)
    - New York State Planning Council, 1937-1942 (Box 19, Folder 368)
    - North Carolina League of Municipalities, 1929-1939 (Box 19, Folder 369)
    - North Carolina League of Municipalities, 1929-1939 (Box 19, Folder 370)
    - North Carolina League of Municipalities - Audits, 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 371)
    - North Carolina League of Municipalities - Reports and Publications (Box 19, Folder 372)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1930-1935 (Box 20, Folder 373)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1930-1935 (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry, 1930-1935 (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry - Reports (Box 20, Folder 376)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry - Reports (Box 20, Folder 377)
    - Regional Planning Association, 1936-1941 (Box 20, Folder 378)
    - Regional Planning Association, 1936-1941 (Box 20, Folder 379)
    - Regional Planning Association, 1936-1941 (Box 20, Folder 380)
    - Regional Planning Association - Reports (Box 20, Folder 381)
    - Social Science Research Council - Commission of Inquiry, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 382)
    - Social Science Research Council - Commission of Inquiry - Reports (Box 21, Folder 383)
    - Special Projects - Atomic Energy (Box 21, Folder 384)
    - Special Projects - Boundary Line Between Politics and Administration, 1945-1948 (Box 21, Folder 385)
    - Special Projects - Civilian Commission on Defense Expenditures, 1948-1949 (Box 21, Folder 386)
    - Special Projects - Emergency Administration Survey, 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 387)
    - Special Projects - Gosnell, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 388)
    - Special Projects - Unemployment Relief, 1931-1947 (Box 21, Folder 389)
    - Special Projects - University of Chicago, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 390)
    - Special Projects - White Report, 1931 (Box 21, Folder 391)
    - State Board of Housing, New York, 1932-1935 (Box 21, Folder 392)
    - State Board of Housing, New York - Reports (Box 21, Folder 393)
    - Special Projects - Hincks, 1933-1934 (Box 22, Folder 394)
    - Special Projects - Hincks - Reports (Box 22, Folder 395)
    - Special Projects - Hincks - Reports (Box 22, Folder 396)
    - Special Projects - Hincks - Reports (Box 22, Folder 397)
    - State Board of Social Welfare, New York, 1932-1936 (Box 23, Folder 398)
    - State Board of Social Welfare, New York, 1932-1936 (Box 23, Folder 399)
    - State Board of Social Welfare, New York - Publications (Box 23, Folder 400)
    - State of New Hampshire, 1931-1935 (Box 23, Folder 401)
    - State of New Hampshire - Report (Box 23, Folder 402)
    - Survey of the Negro in New Jersey, 1930-1933 (Box 23, Folder 403)
    - Survey of the Negro in New Jersey, 1930-1933 (Box 23, Folder 404)
    - Survey of the Negro in New Jersey - Publications (Box 23, Folder 405)
    - Tennessee Department of Institutions, Welfare Department, 1929-1934 (Box 24, Folder 406)
    - Tennessee Department of Institutions, Welfare Department, 1929-1934 (Box 24, Folder 407)
    - Tennessee Department of Institutions, Welfare Department - Publications (Box 24, Folder 408)
    - Texas Joint Legislative Committee, 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 409)
    - Texas Joint Legislative Committee, 1931-1933 (Box 24, Folder 410)
    - Texas Joint Legislative Committee - Publications (Box 24, Folder 411)
    - Texas Joint Legislative Committee - Publications (Box 24, Folder 412)
    - Texas Joint Legislative Committee - Publications (Box 25, Folder 413)
    - Traveling Allotments, 1939-1942 (Box 25, Folder 414)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 415)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 416)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 417)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 418)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 419)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 420)
    - United States Daily, 1929-1935 (Box 25, Folder 421)
    - United States Daily - Trust for Public Administration Clearing House (PACH), 1931-1940 (Box 26, Folder 422)
    - United States Daily - Audits, 1928-1932 (Box 26, Folder 423)
    - United States Daily - Reports (Box 26, Folder 424)
    - United States Daily - Reports (Box 26, Folder 425)
    - United States Daily - Reports (Box 26, Folder 426)
    - United States Daily - Publications (Box 26, Folder 427)
    - United States Employment Service - Job Specification, 1933-1937 (Box 26, Folder 428)
    - United States Employment Service - Job Specification, 1933-1937 (Box 26, Folder 429)
    - United States Employment Service - Job Specification, 1933-1937 (Box 26, Folder 430)
    - United States Employment Service - Job Specification, 1938-1944 (Box 27, Folder 431)
    - United States Employment Service - Job Specification - Reports (Box 27, Folder 432)
    - Virginia Division of the Budget, 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 433)
    - Virginia Division of the Budget, 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 434)
    - Virginia Division of the Budget, 1938-1942 (Box 27, Folder 435)
    - Virginia Division of the Budget - Reports (Box 27, Folder 436)
    - Virginia Division of the Budget - Reports (Box 27, Folder 437)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council, 1934-1936 (Box 27, Folder 438)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council, 1934-1936 (Box 27, Folder 439)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 440)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council - Reports (Box 28, Folder 441)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council - Reports (Box 28, Folder 442)
    - Virginia State Planning Board and Legislative Council - Reports (Box 28, Folder 443)
    - Welfare Council - Employment Study, 1929-1932 (Box 28, Folder 444)
    - Welfare Council - Employment Study - Reports (Box 28, Folder 445)
    - Welfare Council - Employment Study - Reports (Box 28, Folder 446)
  - Projects - "1313" Organizations, 4.2
    - American Association of Public Welfare Officials, 1931-1932 (Box 29, Folder 447)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 448)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 449)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 450)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 451)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 452)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 453)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 454)
    - American Legislators Association, 1929-June 1934 (Box 29, Folder 455)
    - American Legislators Association, July 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 456)
    - American Legislators Association, July 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 457)
    - American Legislators Association, July 1934-1936 (Box 30, Folder 458)
    - American Legislators Association - Audits, 1925-1935 (Box 30, Folder 459)
    - American Legislators Association - Report - "The Legislator," Volume 2, Number 1, March 1929 (Box 30, Folder 459A)
    - American Legislators Association - Report - "Twelve Months with the Legislators - Report of the American Legislators Association", to April 1, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 459B)
    - American Legislators Association - Report - "The Application of the American Legislators Association to the Spelman Fund", 1929 (Box 30, Folder 459C)
    - American Legislators Association - Publications (Box 30, Folder 460)
    - American Legislators Association - Publications (Box 30, Folder 461)
    - American Legislators Association - Publications (Box 31, Folder 462)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 463)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 464)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 465)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 466)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 467)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 468)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 469)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 470)
    - American Municipal Association, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 471)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 472)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 473)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 474)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 475)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 476)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 477)
    - American Municipal Association, 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 478)
    - American Municipal Association - International Congress of Local Authorities, 1931-1935 (Box 32, Folder 479)
    - American Municipal Association - Audits, 1928-1938 (Box 32, Folder 480)
    - American Municipal Association - Audits, 1928-1938 (Box 32, Folder 481)
    - American Municipal Association - Audits, 1939-1948 (Box 33, Folder 482)
    - American Municipal Association - Audits, 1939-1948 (Box 33, Folder 483)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 484)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 485)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 486)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 487)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 488)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 489)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1932-1938 (Box 33, Folder 490)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1939-1945 (Box 34, Folder 491)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1939-1945 (Box 34, Folder 492)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 492A)
    - American Municipal Association - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 492B)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports (Box 35, Folder 493)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports (Box 35, Folder 494)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports (Box 35, Folder 495)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports (Box 35, Folder 496)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports, 10 reports (Box 35, Folder 496A)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports, 14 reports (Box 36, Folder 496B)
    - American Municipal Association - Reports (Box 37, Folder 497)
    - American Municipal Association - Bulletins (Box 37, Folder 498)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 499)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 500)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 501)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 502)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 503)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1930-1937 (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 505)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 506)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 507)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 508)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 509)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 510)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1938-1949 (Box 38, Folder 511)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Audits, 1933-1948 (Box 38, Folder 512)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Audits, 1933-1948 (Box 38, Folder 513)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Audits, 1933-1948 (Box 38, Folder 514)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Annual Reports, 1936-1945 (Box 39, Folder 515)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Annual Reports, 1936-1945 (Box 39, Folder 516)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Annual Report, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 516A)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Annual Report, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 516B)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 516C)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Pamphlets, 10 pamphlets (Box 40, Folder 516)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Pamphlets (Box 40, Folder 517)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Pamphlets (Box 40, Folder 518)
    - American Public Welfare Association - Publications (Box 41, Folder 519)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 520)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 521)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 522)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 523)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 524)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 525)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 526)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 527)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 528)
    - American Public Works Association, 1933-1949 (Box 41, Folder 529)
    - American Public Works Association - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 42, Folder 530)
    - American Public Works Association - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 42, Folder 531)
    - American Public Works Association - Audits, 1935-1948 (Box 42, Folder 532)
    - American Public Works Association - Annual Report, 1935-1948 (Box 42, Folder 533)
    - American Public Works Association - Publications (Box 42, Folder 534)